{
  "extraDescription": "Rounding of terminating decimal expansions",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.008578\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.009",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.00169\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.00",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.04664\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.047",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.1403\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.14",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.4502\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "0.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(97.17\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "97.170",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.7991\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.799",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.0949\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "0.1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.007851\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.008",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(7.702\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "7.70",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(5.451\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "5.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(5.43\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "5.430",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(4.881\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "4.88",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.6325\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.633",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.604\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.60",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.08331\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.08",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.007461\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.007",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.4964\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.496",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.001561\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.002",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.4234\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.42",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.9194\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.92",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.0714\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "0.1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.08643\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.09",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.01103\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.011",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.0646\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "0.1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.155\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.318\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.318",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.9056\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.906",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(7.953\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "7.95",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(6.606\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "6.61",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.09897\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "0.1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.002914\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.00",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.4291\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.43",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.01334\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "0.0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.008797\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.01",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(69.02\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "69.020",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.004595\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.00",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.8249\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.82",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(8.659\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "8.66",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.9207\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.92",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.3785\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.38",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.134\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.13",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(17.56\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "17.560",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(6.298\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "6.3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.6766\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.677",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.832\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.83",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.05318\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.05",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.3507\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.351",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(5.887\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "5.9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(16.83\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "16.830",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.001388\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.001",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.3971\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.40",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(6.336\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "6.34",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(3.351\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "3.4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.0129\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.01",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.8828\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.88",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.06829\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "0.1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.5835\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.58",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.1436\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.14",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(3.901\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "3.90",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.08459\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.08",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.3338\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.334",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(14.83\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "14.830",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(9.798\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "9.80",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(2.595\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "2.6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(9.977\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "10.0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(4.258\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "4.26",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.009677\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "0.0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(9.966\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "9.97",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.002228\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.00",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(14.69\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "14.7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.2663\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.02008\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.02",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(91.58\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "91.6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.793\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.79",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.08394\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.08",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(81.01\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "81.0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(7.769\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "7.8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(22.26\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "22.3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.01707\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.02",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.7074\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.71",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.2735\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.27",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(6.911\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "6.91",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(2.115\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "2.12",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.09946\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "0.1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.08605\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.086",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(50.17\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "50.170",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.75\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "0.8",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(9.368\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "9.37",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.05173\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.052",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.6007\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "0.6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.8326\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.83",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.008691\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.01",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.924\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.924",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.09064\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.09",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.5483\\) to 1 decimal place",
      "answer": "0.5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [1]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.9905\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.99",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(2.579\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "2.58",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.6653\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.665",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.8258\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.826",
      "numberInputTypes": ["dec"],
      "expectedDps": [3]
    }
  ]
}
